<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TradingProject</string>
    <string name="root_url">http://10.0.2.2:3000</string>
    <string name="login_url">/api/login</string>
    <string name="google_signin_url">/api/google-signin</string>
    <string name="forgetpassword_Email">/api/forgot-password</string>
<!--    <string name="default_web_client_id">584554381698-eg56110686ci3qjfl1bunokg6a1l2quc.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>-->


    <string name="appleStock">
        "Apple Inc. designs, manufactures and markets smartphones, personal computers, tablets,
        wearables and accessories, and sells a variety of related services. Its product categories include
        iPhone, Mac, iPad, and Wearables, Home and Accessories. Its software platforms include iOS, iPadOS, macOS, watchOS,
        visionOS, and tvOS. Its services include advertising, AppleCare, cloud services, digital content and payment services.
        The Company operates various platforms, including the App Store, that allow customers to discover and download applications and digital content,
        such as books, music, video, games and podcasts. It also offers digital content through subscription-based services, including Apple Arcade, Apple Fitness+,
        Apple Music, Apple News+, and Apple TV+. Its products include iPhone 16 Pro, iPhone 16, iPhone 15, iPhone 14, iPhone SE, MacBook Air, MacBook Pro, iMac,
        Mac mini, Mac Studio, Mac Pro, iPad Pro, iPad Air, AirPods, AirPods Pro,
        AirPods Max, Apple TV and Apple Vision Pro."
    </string>

    <string name="large_text">
        "       ในช่วงเวลายามเย็นของฤดูฝน อากาศเย็นสบาย ลมพัดเบา ๆ สายฝนโปรยปรายลงมาจากท้องฟ้าสีเทาหม่น กลิ่นดินหอมอบอวลไปทั่วบริเวณ บ้านเรือนเปิดไฟสีส้มส่องแสงอบอุ่นผู้คนเดินถือร่มผ่านถนนที่เปียกชื้น เด็ก ๆ วิ่งเล่นใต้ชายคา หัวเราะสนุกสนานเสียงกบร้องประสานกันจากท้องนาไกล ๆ น้ำฝนไหลตามร่องระบายน้ำเป็นสายยาวพื้นดินชุ่มฉ่ำ ต้นไม้เขียวชอุ่มดูสดชื่น ชาวบ้านบางคนออกมายืนหน้าบ้านมองดูฟ้าที่ครึ้มไปด้วยเมฆฝนรอคอยให้หยาดน้ำสุดท้ายตกลงมาแล้วฟ้ากลับสว่างอีกครั้ง"
    </string>
    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>
</resources>